So now let's update our code so that this request random numbers automatically happens using chain link keepers.
现在让我们来更新代码，使用 "Chainlink keepers" 自动执行这个 "requestRandomWinner"
And if we look at the example contract can actually read more about what's really important for this to work.
如果我们看一下这个示例合约，就可以更多地了解对于这项工作来说真正重要的事情
And we need a check upkeep and a perform upkeep function in our code.
我们需要在代码中实现一个 "checkUpkeep" 和一个 "performUpkeep" 函数
So instead of request random winner, this is going to be the PErforM upkeep that we're going to change.
所以我们不再是使用 "requestRandomWinner" 而是需要把它改成 "performUpkeep"
But first let's make this check upkeep
但首先要做的还是创建 "checkUpkeep"
checkup keep function is basically going to be checking to see is it time for us to get a random number to update the recent winner and to send them all the funds.
"checkUpkeep" 函数就是用来查看是否到了我们该获取随机数，更新最近优胜者，以及给他们打钱的时间了
So let's go ahead and make that function.
让我们来创建一下这个函数
I'm going to add some notes here, just so that it's clear what's going on.
我会在这里添加一些注释，这样可以清晰地说明这里正在发生些什么
And maybe I'll even do natspec To tell developers what's going on with this function.
我甚至可能会使用 "Natspec" (“自然语言规范”)来告诉开发者们这个函数的功能是什么
So we're going to create this function check upkeep.
所以我们来创建这个函数 `function checkUpkeep()`
And if we look at what this needs, it needs to be external override
并且我们可以看一下它需要哪些关键字，它需要的是 "external override"
external override.
`external override`
And if we see this override keyword, this means that okay, there's probably a perform upkeep somewhere else.
我们看一下这个 "override" 关键字，它的意思是可能其它地方还会有一个 "performUpkeep" 方法
And if we scroll to the top, and we're going to import this keeper compatible interface,
我们拉到顶部，这个地方会导入这个 "KeeperCompatibleInterface"
so that we make sure that we implement both check upkeep and perform upkeep in our code here.
这样我们可以确保代码会实现 "checkUpkeep" 以及 "performUpkeep" 这两个方法
If you want you can just import keeper compatible in here or just the keeper compatible interface
如果你想的话，你可以只导入 "KeeperCompatible" 或是直接使用 "KeeperCompatibleInterface"
in our code. We're going to do
在我们的代码中，我们的做法是
import at chain link slash contracts slash SRC slash V 0.8 point two interfaces slash keeper compatible interface that soul
`import "@chainlink/contracts/src/v0.8/interfaces/KeeperCompatibleInterface.sol"
and now we're just gonna say contract raffle is Veera of consumer base V two and keeper compatible interface
现在我们的合约 "Raffle" 就是 "VRFConsumerBaseV2" 以及 "KeeperCompatibleInterface"
and this keeper compatible interface inheritance just make sure that we add checkup keep and perform upkeep,
继承这个 "KeeperCompatibleInterface" 只是为了确保我们添加的有 "checkUpkeep" 以及 "performUpkeep"
which we're going to add in a little bit.
稍后我们再自行添加
And if we look back at the docs we can see checkup keep takes a bytes called Data check data as an input parameter.
我们回来看一下文档，可以发现 "checkUpkeep" 接收一个 "bytes calldata checkData" 作为输入参数
So we'll do bytes called data. Check data as a parameter.
所以我们写下 `bytes calldata checkData` 作为参数
Now this check upkeep bytes call data allows us to specify really anything that we want when we call this check upkeep function.
这个 "bytes calldata" 允许我们在调用 "checkUpkeep" 时指定我们想要指定的任何内容
Having this check data be of type bytes means that we can even specify this to call other functions,
"checkData" 类型为 "bytes" 意味着我们甚至可以指定这里去调用其他函数
there's a lot of advanced things you can do by just having an input parameter as type of bytes
通过将输入参数设置为 "bytes" 类型，你可以实现许多高级功能
for us though, we're going to keep it a little bit simple.
不过，对于我们来说，要做的会简单一些
And we're actually not going to use this check data piece.
实际上，我们并不会使用到这个 "checkData" 部分
So similar to how below we're not using Request ID, we can just comment it out.
就和下面的 "requestId" 类似，我们用不到它，所以就直接给注释掉了
However, we still need to make sure that this parameter is type of bytes called data.
但我们仍然需要确保这里的参数类型是 "bytes calldata"
Now anyways, let's go ahead and annotate this check upkeep function,
不管怎么样，让我们继续对这个 "checkUpkeep" 函数进行注释吧
we'll say this is the function that the chain link keeper nodes call they look for the to return true.
我们说“这个函数由 Chainlink Keeper 节点调用，它们会检查 `upkeepNeeded` 是否返回 true”
Look back at the documentation, we can see that this check upkeep returns both and upkeep needed and to perform data,
我们再看一下文档，可以看到 "checkUpkeep" 同时返回 "upkeepNeeded" 以及 "performData"
which again, we're going to ignore
不过 "performData" 同样也被忽略掉了
this upkeep needed is going to be true or false.
这个 "upkeepNeeded" 可以是 true 或者 false
If it's true, that means it's time to get a new random number
如果它为 true，那么就意味着是时候获取一个新的随机数了
following should be true in order to return true.
要想返回 true，应当满足以下条件
So in order for it to be time to request a random winner, what should happen,
为了能在合适的时机执行 "requestRandomWinner"，应当做些什么呢？
our time interval should have passed, which we haven't defined yet. But we will
我们的时间间隔应当满足，虽然还没定义，但之后会的
lottery should have at least one player and have some eath.
彩票系统里应当至少有一位玩家，并且里面有一些以太币
And then our subscription is funded with Link
然后是，我们的订阅已经注入了 Link 资金
similar to how with channeling Vir f your subscription needs to be funded with Link,
就和使用 Chainlink VRF 订阅时需要使用 Link 资金类似
the same thing needs to happen for check upkeep and keepers to run your subscription needs to be funded with link.
对于 "checkUpkeep" 以及 "Keepers" 来说，订阅同样也需要使用 Link 资金
Now we're going to add one more additional piece here,
我们需要在这里增加一个新的部分
we're going to say for the lottery should be in an open state,
`4.彩票应当处于 "open" 状态`
something that we want to avoid
有一些事是我们想要避免的
when we're waiting for a random number to return. And when we've requested a random winner.
当我们在等待一个随机数返回以及请求了一个随机优胜者时
We're technically in this weird limbo state where we're waiting for a random number to be returned.
实际上，我们正处于一种奇怪的悬而未决的状态，我们正在等待一个随机数的返回
And we really shouldn't allow any new players to join.
此时我们不应该允许任何新玩家加入
So what we actually want to do is create some state variable telling us whether the lottery is open or not.
所以，我们要创建一些状态变量来表明彩票是否正在开放
And while we're waiting for our random number to get back, we'll be in a closed or a calculating state.
而在我们等待随机数返回的期间，我们应当处于关闭或者计算状态